<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News and Resources on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News and Resources on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 14:05:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RSV Update 2019</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-08-09-rsv-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 14:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-08-09-rsv-2019/</guid>
      <description>The following PDF document is the Guidelines for Prophylaxis for RSV Infections in High-Risk Infants in Hawaii which is developed by the Consensus Committee, which is comprised of neonatologists, pediatricians, hospitalists, pediatric intensivists, pediatric specialists, and insurance representatives from various hospital and medical groups on Oahu and the neighbor islands every year prior to the RSV season.
This committee also welcomes comments from community pediatricians and other healthcare providers regarding RSV infections in their practices and the impact of these guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPV Vaccine Videos</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-08-09-hpv-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 14:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018-08-09-hpv-videos/</guid>
      <description>MDH has created a 12-minute video for health care providers on HPV vaccine communication. The video begins with humorous vignettes and then presents four model clinical encounters in which providers demonstrate low-stress ways of recommending HPV vaccine and answering questions from patients and parents. Each of the model encounters can also be viewed individually.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>