<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:21:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Who We Are The Chapter is a voluntary organization of over 300 members in private, group, military and academic practice as well as pediatricians in training and other non-pediatric physicians interested in Child Health issues.
What We Stand For Our mission of the Hawaii Chapter is to attain optimal physical, mental and social health and well-being for infants, children, adolescents and young adults. We will accomplish this mission by addressing the needs of children, their families and their communities, and by supporting Chapter members through advocacy, education, research, service and improving the systems through which they deliver pediatric care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 things that won&#39;t happen in free songs</title>
      <link>/posts/16-things-free-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:21:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/16-things-free-songs/</guid>
      <description>5 ways country song ringtones can make you rich. Why country music festivals will change your life. The unconventional guide to music notes. Why our world would end if music videos disappeared. 8 insane (but true) things about top country songs. How twitter can teach you about popular songs. 13 facts about latin music videos that&amp;rsquo;ll keep you up at night. Why do people think free dances are a good idea?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/join-us/</guid>
      <description>Hawaii Chapter is a forum for member ideas, concerns and communication that impact you at the local as well as national level.
Advocacy HAAP is actively examining the needs of the children we treat as well as the needs of the pediatricians in our community. We have sought to establish dialogue and credibility with those that set health care policy. By joining the chapter one can more effectively participate in making the concerns of pediatricians known and contribute to the work needed to change our health care environment so that we can continuously push to deliver health care for children in a more optimal manner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>